Guide to the John R. Post Collection of Lawrence Clark Powell Material
Department of Special Collections
- Series 3: Miscellaneous
  - From Private Collector to Public Institution: The William Andrew Clark Library April 1950 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    Reprint,Library Quarterly; autographed
  - Adventures in British Libraries and Book Marts 1951 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    Roxburghe Club meeting announcement
  - The Free Flow of Books October 1951 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    Reprint, Library Journal
  - Islands of Books 1951 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    Zamorano Club meeting announcement
  - Islands of Books 1951 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    Prepublication discount for librarians announcment
  - Book Thoughts from Abroad June 1951 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Book Thoughts from Abroad June 1951 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    Califreprintornia Librarian
  - Book thoughts from Oxford Winter 1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    Book Club of California Quarterly Newsletter
  - Book Hunter in Britain March 1951 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - A Librarian on Leave January 1951 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    The Journal of the National Book League (London)
  - A Librarian Takes Stock 1951 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    Antiquarian Booksellers Association, Newsletter no. 15 (London)
  - Multum in Parvo December 1951 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Music into Silence Winter 1951 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    The Pacific Spectator
  - Music into Silence Winter 1951 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    Reprint, The Pacific Spectator; no cover
  - Music into Silence Winter 1951 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    Reprint, The Pacific Spectator; with cover
  - Return to France Summer 1951 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Sentimental Journey September 1951 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - The Alchemy of Books September 1952 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    ALA Bulletin
  - The Alchemy of Books September 1952 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    Reprint, ALA Bulletin
  - Manhattan Winter March 1952 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Midsummer Miscellany September 1952 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Transcontinental June 1952 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Transcontinental June 1952 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - This Dry and Wrinkled Land July 1953 (Box 10, Folder 31)
    Reprint, Arizona Librarian
  - Land of Fiction June 1953 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    Reprint, California Librarian; 2p. typescript list of Western-Southwestern fiction
  - The Power to Evoke Summer 1953 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    Reprint, Manuscripts
  - Stop Thief! June, 1953 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    Reprint of paper delivered at the American Library History Round Table, Los Angeles,appearing the Wilson Library Bulletin, December 1953; Invitation to the Randolph G. Adams Memorial Lecture, Clements Library Associates, October 1953
  - The Alchemy of Books 1954 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    Publication announcement; special edition ordering form
  - Bean Fields, Builders, and Books December 1954 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    The Historical Society of Southern California Quarterly
  - Bean Fields, Builders and Books December 1954 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    Reprint, The Historical Society of Southern California Quarterly; inscribed
  - Bean Fields, Builders and Books December 1954 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    Reprint, The Historical Society of Southern California Quarterly
  - Bean Fields, Builders and Books June 1954 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    Newspaper item announcing talk by L.C.P. before UCLA Faculty Women's Club
  - Books Determine November 1954 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    Southwestern Library Assn 15th Biennial Conference, Papers and Proceedings
  - Learning to Teach, Teaching to Learn October 1954 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Living Librarians IX: Lawrence Clark Powell November 1954 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    ALA Bulletin article by Neil Harlow
  - Magnetic Field December 1954 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    The University of Tennessee, Extension Series: U of T Library Lectures
  - The Purple Dragon 1919 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    The Marengo Literary Leader, December 2, 1919
  - The Purple Dragon 1919 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    The Marengo Literary Leader, December 2, 1919 (2nd copy)
  - La Machine a Ecrive 1935 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    Apertif, vol 1, no. 6 (Santa Barbara)
  - Robinson Jeffers '05 March 1935 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    The Occidental Alumnus
  - Ex Libris Omega Kappa 1936 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Revista Occidental, publication of Omega Kappa Chapter, Phi Gamma Delta, Occidental College, LA
  - The Function of Rare Booksa December 1939 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    Reprint, College and Research Libraries
  - C. C. Mc Intyre March 1939 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    Wilson Bulletin for Librarians
  - Octoberlied October 1939 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    Occidental Alumnus
  - Problem Of Rare Books in College Libraries April 1939 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    The Library Journal
  - Flumgudgeon Gazette in 1845 Antedated the Spectator June 1940 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    Oregon Historical Quaterly
  - "The Western American" - An Early California Newspaper 1940 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    Reprint[?],The Bibliographical Society of America, vol. 34 Fourth Quarter
  - "Ex Libris - Lawrence Clark Powell" 1941 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    Bookplate of L.C. P., 2 copies, attached
  - John Fiske - Bookman 1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    Reprint[?],The Bibliographical Society of America, vol. 34 Reprint[?],The Bibliographical Society of America, vol. 35 Reprint[?],The Bibliographical Society of America, vol. 34 Fourth Quarter
  - Philosopher Pickett June 1942 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    Book review by Prof. John Ellis, The Roman Forum, LA
  - Resources of Western Libraries September 1942 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    Reprint, The Pacific Historical Review
  - An Unpublished Mark Twain Letter January 1942 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    Reprint, American Literature
  - I Read What I Like October 1943 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    Wilson Library Bulletin, Section 1
  - Travel Notes From the Shipping Room May 1944 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - An Almanac for Libraries June 1945 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    Reprint[?], Wilson Library Bulletin
  - We Moderns Summer 1945 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    SCOP, 1st Issue, official literary publication of the Associated Students of UCLA
  - We Moderns November 1945 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ward Ritchie: Printer 1946 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    The Book Collector's Packet, vol. 4, no. 9-10
  - A Tribute to Benjamin F. Selter September 1946 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - A University Librarian Takes Pen in Hand April 1, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    Library Journal
  - Thomas C. Laney, Chronicler of '46 February 1947 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - The Pierian Spring January 1947 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    Newsletter published by the University of California Press, Berkeley
  - Academy Library Notes December1948 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - The Chief Librarian--Bookman of Administration October 1948 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    Stechert-Hafner Book News
  - Policy and Administration 1948 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Rare Books in the University Library: ACRL publication of papers delivered June 17, 1948
  - San Joaquin Vision June 1948 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    reprint, California Library Journal
  - Academic Library Notes March 1949 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    California Library Journal
  - Academic Library Notes June 1949 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Books and People and the Earth on Which We Live August 1949 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    Pacific Northwest Library Association (PNLA) Quarterly, proceedings of 39th Annual Conference
  - The Chief Librarian; Bookman or Administrator? March 1949 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    The Publishers' Circular and Boookseller's Record
  - The Chief Librarian; Bookman or Administrator January 8, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    Antiquarian Bookman
  - In It Together July 9, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - The Magnetic Field of Books 1954 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Lecture announcement, UCLA, July 29, 1954
  - Mitchell of California May 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Mitchell of California 1954 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    Reprint, Wilson Library Bulletin
  - Sky, Sun and Water: The Southwest of Frederick Webb Hodge Spring 1954 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    Southwest Review
  - Sky, Sun and Water: The Southwest of Frederick Webb Hodge 1954 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    Reprint, Southwest Review, inscribed
  - Books Determine September 1955 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    Wilison Library Bulletin
  - Books Determine 1955 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Books of Western Fiction February 1955 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    Invitation to Special Luncheon, Caxton Club, Chicago, IL
  - Books of the Southwest 1955 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    Publication announcement
  - Memorial Addresses at a Service Honoring Ernest Carroll Moore February 1955 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    Booklet, UCLA, February 15, 1955
  - Three Loves Have I February 1955 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    Reprint, Michigan Alumnus Quarterly Review, February 26, 1955
  - Three Loves Have I February 1955 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    Michigan Alumnus Quarterly Review, February 26, 1955
  - West, Southwest, Impressions of Southern Libraries Summer 1955 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    Reprint, The Southwestern Librarian
  - Christmas...The Southwest...and J. Frank Dobie Christmas, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    Printed for the friends of Jack and Rosalie Reynolds
  - The Elements of Fruitfulness November 1956 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    Antiquarian Booksellers Association of America, Bulletin no. 1,autographed
  - Memorial Addresses Honoring Edward Augustus Dickson March 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    UCLA
  - My Favorite Four Letter Word August 1956 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    Southern Observer
  - My Favorite Four Letter Word 1956 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    "The 1956 AB [Antiquitarian Bookman]" Bookman's Yearbook
  - All That Is Poetic in Life: Austin Wright's Islandia May 1957 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - All That Is Poetic in Life: Austin Wright's Islandia May 1957 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Book Collecting and Libraries 1957 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Antiquarian Booksellers Bookman's Yearbook
  - Books of the Southwest June 1957 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    Checklist compiled by LCP, issued by UCLA, no. 1
  - Books Will Be Read 1957 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    Reprint, The Library Associationn Annual Lecture, given Sept 17-20, 1957
  - The Gift To Be Simple 1957 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    Reprint, address given to the South Carolina Library Association, Clemson, October 27, 1956
  - Revista Nueva Mexicano Winter 1957 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    Reprint, Southwest Review
  - Through the Burning Glass September 1957 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Through the Burning Glass September 1957 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Through the Burniing Glass September 1957 (Box 12, Folder 28)
    Reprint, Wilson Library Bulletin, 2nd copy
  - The Way it Sounds to Me Autumn 1957 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - The Way It Sounds to Me Autumn 1957 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Books Will Be Read February 1, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Bookman in Seven League Boots Summer 1958 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Libros Californianos, or, Five Feet of California Books 1958 (Box 12, Folder 32)
    By Phil Townsend Hanna, Revised and Enlarged by LCP. publication announcement
  - A Little Sermon on Binding Jan-Feb 1958 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    The Rub Off, published by the Art Guild Bindery, Inc.
  - Dr. Powell On the Special Libraries Winter 1958 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    Sci-Tech News, Official Bulletin of the Science-Technology Division, Special Libraries Association
  - A Passion for Books 1958 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Rendezvous in Cadogan Square Fall 1958 (Box 12, Folder 36)
    Reprint, from Manuscripts
  - The Sense of the Past December 1958 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    Address given to 75th meeting of the Historical Society of Southern California, reprint, Historical Society of Southern California Quarterly
  - A Southwestern Century March 1958 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - To Touch or Not To Touch September 1958 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - To Touch or Not to Touch September 1958 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Reprint, ALA Bulletin, 2nd copy
  - Administration in One Easy Lesson February 1959 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - The Elements of a Good Librarian September 1959 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Landscapes Wih Books Summer 1959 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Landscape With Books Summer 1959 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - The Library in the Expanding University March 1959 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    Address given beofre the UCLA chapter of the American Association of University Professors
  - Rendezvous in Cadogan Square March 1959 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Antiquarian Booksellers' Association (International) New letter no. 25
  - Return to Heartland June 1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Speaking of Books February 7, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    Reprint, NY Times Book Review
  - Speaking of Books February 7, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    Reprint, NY Times Book Review, 2nd copy
  - Little Package Fall 1961 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    Arizona Librarian
  - Go Forth and Be Usefull 1962 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    Valedictory Address, SAchool of Library Service, Class of 1962
  - On Giving and Getting Books January - February 1962 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - The Prospect Before Us December 8, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    The Book Club of California, Fiftieth Anniversary Dinner announcement, L.C.P speaker of the evening
  - Robinson Jeffers '05 1963 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    Impromptu, a Faculty-Alumni Publication of Occidental College
  - Talisman for Travelers Autumn 1962 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Shake Well and Speak July 15, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - The Lure of Californiana 1964 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    The Book Club of California Quaretly News, Fall 1964; reprint, The California Librarian, July, 1964
  - In Search of Spring Winter, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - The Way West 1964 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    Rodgers Library Notes, New Mexico Highlands University, October 1963 - July 1964
  - A World That is Wide and Wonderful 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    A Wrold That is Wide and Wonderful
  - A World That's Wide and Wonderful January 6, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    The New York Times Book Review
  - The Writer in an Automatic World April 1964 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Checklist of Writings of L.C.P. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    School of Library Service, UCLA; autographed
  - A Convocation at UCLA Honoring L.C.P. on His Retirement June 1966 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    Announcement
  - Musical Bloodbrothers April 1966 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Announcement, Spring Meeting, Library Patrons of Occidental College
  - The Elements of a Good Librarian 1966 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    Occidental College Alumnus, Winter 1967; reprint of address given to Indiana and Ohio Library Associations
  - Writings About Jeffers August 1967 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    "Robinson Jeffers: A Checklist," compiled by Robert Brophy, Gleeson Library, University of San Francisco; L.C.P. work included on list.
  - From Monterey to San Simeon: Jeffers, Miller, and Brother Antoninus Winter 1967 (Box 13, Folder 27)
    Western Review
  - Mary Hunter Austin Spring 1968 (Box 13, Folder 28)
    Arizona and the West, A Quarterly Journal of History
  - Bookman's Progress 1968 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Climbing the Ladder January 1968 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Dawson's Bookshop New Store Reception 1968 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    Announcement; L.C.P. on hand to commemorate the occasion
  - Fortune and Friendship: An Autobiography by L.C.P.; Promotonal Piece 1968 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - An Interview with L.C.P. October 1968 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    Bay State Librarian
  - Los Angeles Bibliography 1968 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    Booksellers and Librarians Edition, compiled for "Los Angeles," A Sunset Book, Lane magazine and Book Co.
  - The Makings of a Bookman 1968 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    Book revew of Fortune and Friendship, Bookman's Weekly, September 23, 1968
  - Lawrence Clark Powell Fall, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    Arizona Librarian, issued dedicated to L.C.P., includes four essays by L.C.P.
  - The Example of Miss Edith Coulter 1969 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    Seventeenth Coulter Lecture announcement, given at the California Library Association Conference, San Diego, CA, October 25, 1968
  - Dukedom Large Enough 1969 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    Book review by L.C.P. of title authored by David A. Randall, NY Times Book Review, August 31, 1969
  - Checklist of Writings of L.C.P. 1966 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    School of Library Service, UCLA; inscribed
  - 200 Books of California's 200th Anniversary 1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    List compiled by California Library Association, L.C.P. works listed, p. 1.
  - California Classics Reread or "There's Gold in Those Books" 1970 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    Lecture announcement, UC-Davis, Sunday, April 12, 1970
  - Writings About Jeffers 1970 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    Exhibit announcement, CSU-San Luis Obispo, April 1970; L.C.P. cited on p. 3.
  - Charles Fletcher Lummis and The Land of Sunshine 1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Reprint, Westways, January, 1970
  - Charles Fletcher Lummis and The Land of Sunshine 1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Photocopy of letter accompanying preceding, from John H. Kemble, President, the Historical Society of Southern California, March 9, 1970
  - The Abiding Legacy 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Remarks on the occasion of hte dedication of the addition to the Mary Norton Clapp Library, Occidental College, January 20, 1971
  - Los Angeles Library Association Tribute to L.awrence and Fay Powell. 1971 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Announcement, annual tribute luncheon, Alexandria Hotel, April 19, 1971
  - A Tribute To Bradford Booth 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Address given to the Firends of UCLA Library; 2 copies
  - Ralph D. Cornell and U.C.L.A. October 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    California Horticultural Journal
  - John E. Goodman, Founder of the UCLA Library: An Essay Toward a Biography 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Friends of the UCLA Library, reprinted from The Journal of Library History, July 1971
  - A Backward Look Ahead November 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    The UCLA Monthly, UCLA Alumni Association
  - Song of the Southwest 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Historical Society of Southern California, reprinted from Westways, January 1973
  - Libraries and Scholarship, A Conference at the University of Arizona, Tucson 1974 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Announcement and reservation form, L.C.P. presiding on November 23, 1974
  - Powell Lecture 1974 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Invitation, Powell address to The Friends of Occidental College, March 19, 1974
  - The Southwest of the Traveling Reader Summer 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Occidental, publication of Occidental College
  - Three Signed Holgraph Letters to Henry Miller 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    Dated 1/24/1975; 11/21/1975; 1/26/1976
  - Lawrence Clark Powell at 70 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    Bookman's Weekly, October 18,1976
  - What Does a Library Want To Be When it Grows Up 1976 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Announcement, Friends of the Library, dedication of remodeled UC-Irvine Library, L.C.P. featured speaker, June 13, 1976
  - The Desert - - John C. Van Dyke 1976 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Publication announcement, introduction by L.C.P.
  - The Blue Train February 1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - The Enchanted Couple 1977 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Meeting announcement, Gleeson Library Associates, USF, May 1, 1977, L.C.P. guest speaker
  - John Muir: A Reading Bibliography 1977 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    Compiled by William and Maymie Kimes, foreword by L.C.P.
  - The Professor and the Poet 1979 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    Announcement, dinner and program, the library Patrons of Occidental College, L.C.P. speaker, April 2, 1979
  - Henry Miller June 1980 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    UCLA Librarian
  - Keepsake 75th Birthday 1981 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    Keepsake and announcement, Friends of the UCLA Library, September 3, 1981
  - The Library as Sanctuary 1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    The Pasadena Public Library: A History, 1895-1982
  - Jake Zeitlin at Eighty Autumn 1982 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Reprint, The Book Collector
  - Andrew Harlis Horn: Professor and Dean of Library and Infomation Science, UCLA 1983 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    Obituary, attributed to Russell Shank, Robert Vosper, and Robert Kinsman; L.C.P. mentioned in text; publication unknown
  - The Long Commitment 1983 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    Address delivered to Annual Conference of the Colorado Library Assn.
  - A Sense of the Future 1983 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    Address given before the Historical Society of Southern California; photocopy of ts, inscribed
  - El Morro 1984 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Publication announcement and book store event, May 4, 1984
  - Lecture on Learning, by Charles D. Poston 1985 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Reprint of lecture, Friends of the University of Arizona Library; foreword by L.C.P.
  - Books are Basic:The Essential Lawrence Clark Powell January 1986 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    Short review of collection edited by John David Marshall; Antiquitarian Bookman, Bookman's Weekly, January 6, 1986
  - Lawrence Clark Powell at Eighty September 1986 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    Editor's Corner essay, Antiquitarian Bookman, Bookman's Weekly, September 1, 1986
  - Powell to Lecture March 1986 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    Library Notes, Antiquitarian Bookman, Bookman's Weekly, (p 1442), March 31, 1986
  - Portrait of My Father September 1986 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    Publication announcement and reception to celebrate L.C.P.'s 80th Birthday,; Joe the Pro's new studio, Santa Barbara, September 3, 1986
  - On The Typographical Taos Trail June 1986 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    Bibliograhical Notes essay, Antiquitarian Bookman, June 23, 1986
  - Robinson Jeffers, Poet 1887- 1987: A Centennial Exhibition 1987 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    OcciNext to Mother's Milkdental College exhibit booklet; L.C.P. work cited in select bibiliography, photo on p. 32
  - Next to Mother's Milk Summer / Fall1987 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    Occidental: The Quarterly Publication of Occidental College, Summer/Fall 1987
  - F. D. R.: A Selected Bibliography of the Zeitlin Franlin Delano Roosevelt Collection May 1988 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    Keepsake, compiled by Michael C. Sutherland, preface by L.C.P., dedication and dinner honoring donation of collection, Library Patrons of Occidental College, May 11, 1988
  - Determined Donor: T. Edward Hanley and His Gift of Books to the University of Arizona librarey 1936 - 1964 1989 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    Keepsake, by Lee Sorensen, foreword by L.C.P.; Freinds of the University of Arizona Library
  - The Fellows Award Program Of The Historical Society of Southern California (Box 14, Folder 42)
    Keepsake, L.C.P. named a Fellow of the Society
  - Lawrence Clark Powell 1992 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    Text by Gerald Hslam; Western Writers Series #102, Boise State University; autographed
  - Yeats in My Old Age 1993 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Reprint Keepsake, originally appeared in Hoja Volante, February _ May, 1993; autogrpahed
  - Books West Southeest 1994 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    Publication announcement, celebration of L.C.P.'s 88th birthday
  - Lawrence Clark Powell, Bookman by Joel Silver January 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    Annals of Bibliography, Antiquitarian Bookman, Bookman's Weekly, January 31, 1994
  - Paul Horgan - Frank Waters 1995 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    Memorial Exhibition booklet, the University of Arizona Library; foreword by L.C.P., autographed
  - Book Club of California Oscar Lewis Award to L.C.P. 1996 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    Page torn from Bookquote, no 155, January 19, 1996
  - Fashioned in Friendship: Lawrence Clark Powell as Designed by Ward Ritchie 1996 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    Exhibition announcement ,in celebration of L.C.P.'s 90th birthday, the University of Arizona Library, through September 1996; obituary of Karl Zamboni, torn from SF Chronicle, L.C.P. mentioned, February 1, 1997
  - The Glowing Heart of the World 1998 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    Trade Reviews, Antiquitarian Bookman, Bookman's Weekly, October 5, 1998
  - The Librarian Who Reads 1998 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    Article by Roy Meader in Biblio, p 36, September 1998
  - The Southwest Book Awards: The First 25 Years 1998 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    Bibliography produced by Border regional Library Association; L.C.P. items 28 and 53